fashionphile.com 2019-12-08

# Fashionphile | Privacy

**        Privacy Policy**

        Last Revised: November 27, 2019

        This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how Fashionphile, LLC (“Fashionphile,” “us” or “we”) collects, uses and discloses information from its users, including with respect to the website located at https://www.fashionphile.com/ (the “Website”) and any related content, features, content, materials, applications, widgets and/or services (collectively, the “Services”). 

        BY USING THE SERVICES, YOU ACCEPT ALL OF THE PROVISIONS OF THE FASHIONPHILE TERMS OF USE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THE FASHIONPHILE TERMS OF USE AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THEN YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO USE ANY OF FASHIONPHILE’S SERVICES. 

        For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “you” and “your” means you as the user of the Services. If you use the Services on behalf of a company, organization, or other entity, then “you” includes you and that entity.

        We may collect the following categories of information about you that either directly or indirectly identifies you or could reasonable be used to identify you (collectively, “Personal Information”):

**        Types of Information We Collect**

        Registration information you provide when you create an account, including your name, email address, telephone number, address, username, password, payment information, and other account information.

        Information you provide to us when you access or use the Services and each time you interact with the Services or Fashionphile, for example, when you update information in your control panel, communicate with us by telephone or email, and order products or services. Such information includes your payment information. We also store information about the products you purchase or sell through the Services, such as the product information, date of purchase or sale, and information relating to any support issue.

        Usage, viewing and technical data, including your IP address or device identifier when you use the Services. If you access your account from a mobile device, that mobile device may also provide us with details of your location. Most mobile devices allow you to disable this functionality.

        Information we receive from third parties, including analytics platforms, social media platforms, and advertising partners. For example, if you access the Services through a third party platform or log-in, we may also collect your email address associated with that third party, and any information you have made public in connection with that service or which the third party shares with partner services.

**        How We Collect Your Information**

        You may disable cookies by changing the settings on your browser. Check the help menu in your browser for further information. Remember that if you disable cookies it is likely to affect how the Services work and you may not be able to access or use certain areas of our Website or functionality. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will place cookies when you log on to the Services. To learn more about cookies, as well as your choices with respect to cookies, please visit <https://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. 

        Information You Provide. We collect information you provide to us when you register with us, submit products to us, request products, services or information from us, participate in activities through the Services, respond to customer surveys, or otherwise interact with us. Please keep in mind that when you post information on a third party site or platform, the information you provide may be separately collected by the third party site or platform. The information we collect is covered by this Privacy Policy and the information the third party site or platform collects is subject to the third party site or platform’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you make on the third party site or platform will not apply to our use of the information we collect directly through our Services.

        Unique Identifiers. We collect information through unique identifiers (such as IP address or your mobile device advertising identifier).

        Cookies. We use “cookies” and other technologies to collect data that enable us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our Website. Cookies are files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. We use cookies to gather general information about your visits to our Website, the files you have designated for backup, the configuration of your computer and your computer’s interaction with the Services, and stores this information in log files. Fashionphile uses this information to understand traffic and downloads on our Website, enabling us to improve the Website, provide the best online experience possible, and improve our customer service. We use the following types of cookies on our site: 

        Strictly Necessary Cookies - These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around our Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website and remembering which files you have marked for backup. Without these cookies, services you have asked for, like security or e-billing, cannot be provided.

        Other Technologies - We may also use other Internet technologies, such as web beacons or pixel tags and other similar technologies, to deliver or communicate with cookies and analyze your use of the Services. We also may include web beacons in email messages so that we know when you have opened an email message received from Fashionphile.

        Third Party Analytics. We use third parties’ analytic and tracking tools to better understand who is using the Services, how people are using the Services and how to improve the effectiveness of the Services and their content, and to help those parties serve more targeted advertising to you across the Internet or help us serve more targeted advertising to you. Those third party companies may use cookies, pixel tags or other technologies to collect and store certain information, such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the Services, device identifiers, type of operating system used and other website(s) you may have visited. They might combine information they collect from your interaction with our Services with Personal Information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, nor control over, third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies. We use Google Analytics, which is a web analytics tool that helps us understand how users engage with the Website. Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track user interactions, as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how users use our site. This information is used to compile reports and to help us improve our Website. The reports disclose website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.   

        Do Not Track. Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. Fashionphile and the Services do not recognize DNT. 

**        How We Use Your Information**

        We may use your data for the following purposes where it is in our interests to do so, in order to provide the Services in accordance with the Terms of Use, or where we are legally required:

        To provide you with the Services and the products and services you request.

        To administer your Fashionphile account.

        To communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about features of the Services or changes to our policies.

        To process payments. 

        To ensure consistency with local law and choices and controls that may be available to you. 

        To personalize content and experiences and advertising.

        To detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.

        To optimize or improve the content, products, services, and features of the Services.

        To personalize and improve the Services and user experiences, to increase the functionality and user friendliness of the Services, to deliver content or features that match user profiles or interests.

        To monitor and analyze the Services usage and trends and otherwise measure the effectiveness of the Services.

        We, or third parties with whom we contract or partner, may also send you offers and promotions for our or their products and services (although where required by applicable law, we and they will only do so with your consent or give you the ability to opt-out, as applicable).

**        Sharing Your Information with Other Companies**

        We may share your Personal Information in the following circumstances: 

        Where you direct us to share your Personal Information with third party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites.

        With third party partners for marketing purposes.

        When we contract or partner with a third party to provide services on our behalf, including Services development and maintenance, storage, IT support, advertisers and advertising networks, payment processing, analytics and search engine providers.

        With our affiliates, investors or other third parties in connection with the sale of or other investment in our business (including merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a material portion of its assets, change in corporate control, or insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) or a commercial relationship, and such third parties may separately market to you based on the information provided. 

        To enforce our Terms of Use or rules, to ensure the safety and security of our users and third parties, to protect our rights and property and the rights and property of our users and third parties, to comply with legal process, including judicial warrant, rule, order or subpoena or in other cases if we believe in good faith that disclosure is required by law or regulation.

        In addition, we may share information about groups or categories of users. You will not be personally identifiable from such information. If you would like more information about the companies with whom we share your data, please contact us at info@fashionphile.com.

        We are based in the US so if you are based outside the US, your information will be transferred to the US.  We also process Personal Information on our servers in many countries around the world so your Personal Information may not be processed on a server located in the country in which you live.

Your Controls and Choices

        In certain circumstances, we provide you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding our collection, use and sharing of your information. In accordance with local law, your controls and choices may include:

        You may correct and update your registration account.

        You may change your choices for newsletters and alerts and other direct marketing.

        You may request access to the Personal Information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it or transfer it to someone else.

        You may ask us to stop using or sharing or otherwise dealing with your Personal Information in certain circumstances.   

        You may change your mind where you have provided us with consent and withdraw consent for our use of your Personal Information. 

        You may exercise your controls and choices by modifying your profile or by contacting us at info@fashionphile.com or following instructions provided in communications sent to you. Please be aware that if you do not allow us to collect Personal Information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain products and services to you, and some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If you have questions regarding the specific Personal Information about you that we process or retain, please contact us at info@fashionphile.com. Where relevant and applicable, you also have the option to make a claim with the privacy regulator in the country where you live or work or where you think we have infringed data protection laws.

**        Third Party Websites and Links**

        Our Services may contain links to other sites operated by third parties. Fashionphile does not control such other sites and is not responsible for their content, their privacy policies, or their use of personal information. Fashionphile’s inclusion of such links does not, by itself, imply any endorsement of the content on such sites or of their owners or operators except as disclosed on the Services. Fashionphile expressly disclaims any and all liability for the actions of third parties, including, but without limitation to actions relating to the use and/or disclosure of personal information by third parties. Any information submitted by you directly to these third parties is subject to these third parties’ privacy policies.

**        Children’s Privacy**

        Fashionphile does not intentionally gather any Personal Information about individuals who are under the age of eighteen (18) or knowingly allow such persons to sign up for the Services. The Services are not directed at children under the age of eighteen (18). IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES.

        If Fashionphile becomes aware that it has collected Personal Information from someone under the age of eighteen (18), we will delete such information. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of eighteen (18) who has provided us with Personal Information, you may contact us using the information below to request it be deleted.

**        Data Security, Integrity and Retention**

        General. The security, integrity and confidentiality of your information are important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures that are designed to protect user information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, and modification. From time to time, we review our security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. 

        Retention. We will retain your Personal Information for the length of time needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required, or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims, or for legitimate businesses purposes, or as provided by law.

        Secure Payments. To provide secure credit card processing when ordering from us, orders placed on our Website are processed through a payment gateway which operates under its own privacy policy. If you choose to purchase any products or services online using a credit card, the credit card information is sent to Fashionphile using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption, an industry-standard method for protecting data as it travels over the Internet, or a similar encryption technology that may become accepted as an industry standard, or better encryption method, in the future. To learn more about our credit card processing vendors and their respective privacy and other policies which apply when you make a payment through their services, please review the terms of their own privacy policies.

**        Changes to this Privacy Policy**

        From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements, or for other purposes. If these changes are material, we will provide notice to you by email at the last email address you provided us, by posting notice of such changes on the Services, or by other means, consistent with applicable law. Where required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent for such changes. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, including any changes thereto, then you MAY not use ANY OF the Services.

**        Your California Privacy Rights**

        This Privacy Policy describes how we may share your information for marketing purposes. It applies to all users of the Services, including California residents. We share information with other parts of our business, our service providers, and others, as more fully set forth above.

        Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83 – 1798.84, California residents are entitled to request certain details about how their Personal Information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. To obtain information regarding the categories of Personal Information shared, as well as the names and addresses of third parties with whom Personal Information was shared during the prior calendar year, you may contact us at the information below. Please allow 30 days for a response.

**        Dispute Resolution**

        Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of Personal Information should be directed to Fashionphile at info@fashionphile.com. Fashionphile will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Personal Information in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy. 

        If Fashionphile is unable to resolve your complaint, you can escalate the issue in accordance with the dispute resolution procedure set forth in our Terms of Use or make a claim with the privacy regulator in the country in which you think we have infringed privacy laws.

**        Contact Us**

        You may contact us regarding the Services or this Privacy Policy at: 6359 Paseo Del Lago, Carlsbad, CA 92011 or by email at info@fashionphile.com.
